Guide to the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees Records WAG.238
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1955-2003
  - Overseas Copy Desk, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Overtime Exemptions, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Part-time IAPE Employees, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Part-timers, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Pay Discrimination, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Pay Scales, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Personnel Corporation of America, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Personnel Equivalency Code, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Petitions, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Phase Two, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Policies and Practices, 1992-1997 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Pressmen and Mailers, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Production Coordinator, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Production/Multimedia Technical Specialist, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Profit Sharing Plan, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Proxy Fight, Sep 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Proxy Proposals, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Radio, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Relocation: Full-time Domestic Transfer, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Relocations, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Repetitive Stress Injury Claims, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Report: Background and Future of IAPE, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Reporters Overtime (I), 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Reporters Overtime (II), 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reporters Overtime (III), 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reporters Overtime (IV), 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Reporters Overtime (V), 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Retail Incentive, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Retail Sales Amenity Program, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Retail Sales Department: Telephone Marketing, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Retail Sales Department: Telephone Marketing, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Retirees Dues Deductions, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - ROP Incentive Plan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - ROP Sales, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Rutgers University, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Salary Analysis, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sales: Incentive Plans, 1983-1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Search Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Secretary-Treasurer Levy Scandal, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Seniority, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sexual Discrimination, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Shareholder Issues, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Shareholder Meeting Transcripts, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Shareholder Proposals, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Shareholder Proposals, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Shareholder Resolution Press Conference, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Shift Differential Paid,Full-time, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sienkiewicz, Peter: Dismissal Case, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Smoking Policy (I), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Smoking Policy (II), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Staff Organizer, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Standby Pay, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stockholder Proposal, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Survey, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Taxi Policy, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Teleconference, Jun 26, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Teleconference: Bylaws, Nov 15, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Telemarketing, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Telemarketing, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Telemarketing Layoffs, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Telemarketing Wages, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Telerate, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Telerate/Dow Jones Markets, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Television, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Television Agreement, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Television Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Terbell Partners, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Testing Analysts, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Time Contract, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Training Program, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Transportation Benefits, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Unfair Labor Practices, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Union Bargaining Team, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Union Employees: Full-time, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Union Employees: Part-time, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Union Meetings Held on Company Property (I), 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Union Meetings Held on Company Property (II), 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Union Meetings Held on Company Property (III), 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Union Time-off, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Unity Council of Dow Jones, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Unity Council of Dow Jones, 1993-2000 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Video Display Terminals (VDT's), 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Wade, Frederick (esq.): Memos, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Wage Agreements, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Wage Settlement, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Work and Family Initiatives, 1992-1999 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Series III: Photographs and Buttons, circa 1986-2000
  Series contains approximately 1400 photographs of demonstrations, conferences, dinners, formal events, as well as portraits and documentary photographs, involving the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees (IAPE) and the Communications Workers of America (CWA) from 1986 until circa 2000. Consists mostly of 4x6 black-and-white and color snapshots with corresponding negatives distributed throughout approximately 47 envelopes, as well as over 100 8x10 portraits and candid documentary photographs of IAPE members.
  The series also includes nine buttons featuring IAPE, CWA, and IAPE-CWA insignia.
  - B/W 8x10 Prints [Includes Wall Street Journal Demonstration], undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - B/W Snapshots, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - B/W Snapshots [The Wall Street Journal], Apr 1986, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - B/W Snapshots, Oct 1995-Oct 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - B/W Snapshots [1 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - B/W Snapshots [2 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Candid/Group, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Color Snapshots, circa 1992, 1997, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Color Snapshots, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Color Snapshots [Includes Convention 2000 Photographs] (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Color Snapshots, Loose, Various Demonstrations and Events, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [1 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [Includes Buttons] [2 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [3 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [4 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [5 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Demonstrations [6 of 6], undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Color Snapshots, Various Formal Events, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - IAPE Photos/Portraits, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Loose Negatives, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Medium B/W Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Untitled Folder [Wall Street Journal Demonstration, Conference], undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Series IV: Archived Website, Mar 1, 2013-ongoing
  The Independent Association of Publishers' Employees Inc. (IAPE) was founded 1937 by a group of Dow Jones & Company employees in Manhattan, NY. It has grown to represent employees at various parts of Dow Jones & Company in many locations across the North American continent. In 1997, by vote of the membership, IAPE became Local 1096 of the Communications Workers of America (CWA). Subsequently, IAPE joined The Newspaper Guild sector of the CWA by action of the Board of Directors. The website contains bylaws, grievances, benefits, budgets, their contract, meeting minutes, and news.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.